# Paulina Tuveland UX Designer





4 August 1990 Portfolio - Paulina Tuveland



073 838 04 76



Paulina.tuveland@hotmail.com



<u>LinkedIn - Paulina Tuveland</u>



Gustav III:s väg 113 168 39 Bromma

## Education

UX design, Nackademin

August 2020 – May 2022

Cognitive science classes, Umeå University (AI)

August 2018 - June 2019

- Perception (7,5 p)
- Knowledge and memory (7,5 p)
- Reasoning and information processing (7,5 p)
- Human action (7,5 p)
- Scientific thinking (7,5 p)
- Statistics and empirical method (7,5 p)
- Logic and formal methods (7,5 p)

Web development 7,5 p. (Remote) Luleå University

January 2018 - June 2018

## **Profile**

Newly graduated UX Designer from Nackademin. I analyze problems and design user friendly solutions. I work according to the Design Thinking Process and always start from research.

I have been working with behavioral change since 2016. In addition to coaching members, I have coached my team in the role of personal trainer and group instructor. I feel that I have been given this role as I take responsibility for my team and have a drive for myself and those around me to get a little better every day.

## Work experience

#### **Internship**

UX designer Insurance company Gjensidige February 2022- April 2022

UX researcher Pension organization AMF – Arbetsmarknadsförsäkringar March 2021- May 2021

> Cooperations with companies via Nackademin

UX researcher Scania Part time

October 2020- December 2020

UX researcher Climate View Part time

September 2020- October 2020

#### Other work experience

#### Health coach & Personal trainer, Itrim

February 2017– now (With exceptions between August 2018- June 2019 when I was studying in Umeå)

- Head of personal trainers
- Sales manager
- Group instructor
- Develop workshops

#### Coach & Personal trainer, True Workout

August 2016 - February 2017

- Personal trainer and group instructor

#### Administrator, Försäkringskassan

June 2010 - May 2011

# Language

Swedish	
English	
	_
Sign language	

## Code & Ux tools

HTML & CSS	
Miro, Mural	
Figma, Xd, Sketch	

# Other life experience

#### Hackathon

10-12 June 2022

I Participated in a Hackathon event called **Healthtech** together with my team we created a service called **Clare**.



#### Lecture

August 2019 & February 2020

My own lecture **Motivation for Exercise**, both lectures have been fully booked.

I have had the opportunity to hold these at my workplace, as my employer Itrim Södermalm has increased the number of paying members with the customer evenings held together with my lectures.

### Workshops

November 2019 - February 2020

A colleague and I have developed and run educational workshops focusing on osteoarthritis.

These workshops have been fully booked and due to the pressure we have also been able to create a six-week PT group where the focus has been on in-depth training on this topic. Unfortunately, we had to pause all sessions in the spring of 2020 due to covid-19.